travel-library.com 2013-07-23

# Privacy Policy - Travel-Library

## Privacy Policy

The following statement sets out the policy of Travel Library (travel-library.com) regarding the use of any personal information that we may collect about you, the User.

### 1\. Introduction

When making submissions to Travel Library and when using other services on our Web Site (www.travel-library.com), you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name, the country from which you are posting and your e-mail address). In some cases these details must be entered into the fields provided and in others they are optional Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy.

### 2\. Use and Storage of your Personal Information

Other than a name and country from which you are posting, which you are asked to supply for inclusion in the text of the submissions that you make to our Web Site, the personal information that we collect about you will not be published on our Web Site and will be stored by us for our purposes only. We respect your personal data and are committed to protecting your privacy and we take all reasonable steps to keep your details safe. We will not share your information with others without your prior consent. However, if you provide us with your e-mail address we may use it to supply you with information about Travel Library including but not limited to news about travel offers and changes to our Web Site. While we will not normally pass on your details to anyone else, we reserve the right to disclose any material under our control, including personal data about you, to a relevant person or authority if you breach our Terms and Conditions of Use (<http://www.travel-library.com/terms.html>) and/or when required by statute, rule of law in England and Wales or court order or when such disclosure is requested by the police or other competent regulatory authority or is necessary for the purpose of any civil or criminal legal proceedings.

### 3\. Privacy Policies of Third Parties

Our Web Site contains links to other web sites not owned operated or under the control of Travel Library. These sites will not in general operate the same privacy policies as us and you are therefore advised to carefully read the relevant policies pertaining to these sites before submitting any personal information.

Travel Library has a number of strategic partnerships with reputable third party travel consolidators offering a variety of travel services. Any personal information (including financial data) submitted by our Users through our Web Site to these companies will be transmitted securely and directly to the companies in question. Travel Library will not normally have access to this information.

### 4\. Guidelines for Children

While Travel Library welcomes users of all ages, in line with the recommendations of the TRUSTe children’s programme ([http://www.truste.org](http://www.truste.org/ "Online Trust, Online Safety & Privacy Services from TRUSTe")) , we advise against children under the age of 13 submitting any content to our Web Site. Also, if you are aged 16 or under, we advise that you obtain your parent/guardian's permission before providing any personal information to us. Users under 16 without this permission should not provide us with any personal information.

### 5\. Contact

If you have any questions or queries about our privacy policy, please contact Us.
